Chad D. Lewine | 215.527.8979 | chadlewine@gmail.com 395 S. 2nd St #6 Brooklyn, NY 11211

Career Summary

Accomplished design and digital marketing professional with a proven ability to take ideas and turn them into effective and aesthetically pleasing visual designs. Have a strong history in both digital art and web design, combining to create immersive and powerful graphics & interface designs. Ability to produce results in team and individual environments. Born leader. Conduct ongoing research and development of digital media strategies that help grow brands on and offline.

Work History

Digital Media & Consulting 2002 - Present

http://CDL500.com

- Consistently increasing visual and social appeal of brands in the digital space.
- Improvement of client image and marketing material through websites, web ads, posters, banners, signs, email marketing, video editing, and social media.
- Clients include Brooklyn Night Bazaar, United Way, Saint Gobain/CertainTeed (Full client list on website or available upon request)

Music Producer & Artist 2009 - present

http://HoneyChrome.net

 Designed 5 years of visual campaigns for creative release of music, videos, albums, concerts, etc. i.e. The Chocolate Album product design

Domino Street 2012

http://dominostreetapp.com/

- Responsible for concept and design of thousands of content items each month
- Supported developer on user experience and interface design
- Had several ideas implemented into releases of the application

Blue Fountain Media 2011

SEO Marketing & Social Media Specialist

- Web ad design
- Social media design

<u>Skills</u>

Digital marketing campaigns, all social media, traditional marketing, account management, internet & wireless technologies, email marketing, SEO, HTML, CSS, file sharing, digital music platforms, relationship nurturing, web design, WordPress, Google, Microsoft, Mac, Ableton, Adobe Photoshop, video editing, lyrics, production, composition, event planning, public speaking, hip hop dancing

Education

Art Institute of Pittsburgh 2008 - 2010 Web Design & Interactive Media - Associate of Science

Bachelor's of Arts in equivalent work experience

North Penn High School Graduated 2007 - Lansdale, PA

Client References

Tim Philpot - United Way - 215.584.0887

Aaron Broudo - Brooklyn Night Bazaar - 914.924.9883

Manoj Aggarwal - Domino Street - 917.531.5232

Franco Verdino - FasTracKids - 347.907.9509

Nancy Lewine - GoldenSoul Dogs - 215.896.3770